{
	"1" : {
		"question": "The peanut is a type of nut.",
		"answer": false
	},

	"2" : {
		"question": "To tell someone to \"break a leg\" is a way to wish them good luck.",
		"answer": true
	},

	"3" : {
		"question": "The control ropes to position sails on a ship are called masts.",
		"answer": false
	},

	"4" : {
		"question": "Agoraphobia is the fear of spiders.",
		"answer": false
	},

	"5" : {
		"question": "Audiences in ancient Greece would slap their thighs instead of clapping to show their appreciation for a performance.",
		"answer": false
	},

	"6" : {
		"question": "The average flight altitude of a commercial aircraft is 30,000 feet.",
		"answer": true
	},

	"7" : {
		"question": "John Glenn became the first American to orbit the Earth in 1962.",
		"answer": true
	},

	"8" : {
		"question": "New York City is nicknamed \"Sin City\".",
		"answer": false
	},

	"9" : {
		"question": "Ambidextrous means being able to do something equally well with both hands.",
		"answer": true
	},

	"10" : {
		"question": "Pablo Picasso piloted the first powered airplane with a flight of 120 feet lasting 12 seconds in Kitty Hawk, North Carolina.",
		"answer": false
	}

}